http://www.tdtnews.com/site/privacy.html

Temple, TX
(76501)
Today
Partly cloudy skies this evening will give way to occasional showers overnight. Low 58F. Winds S at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 40%..
Tonight
Partly cloudy skies this evening will give way to occasional showers overnight. Low 58F. Winds S at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 40%.
Site
Temple Daily Telegram Privacy PolicyThe Temple Daily Telegram is committed to respecting your privacy rights when visiting its website. To protect your Personal Information, The Temple Daily Telegram has created the guidelines outlined below. Understanding that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, any changes to this policy will be promptly posted on this page, with an updated “effective date” at the bottom of the page. Information Collected While visiting www.tdtnews.com (hereinafter referred to as the “Site”), we may ask you to register and/or provide information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”) for purposes of interacting with the Site. Such Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, street address, and e-mail address. On any page that collects Personal Information, we will specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service, enter you in the promotion you have requested, or respond to your inquiry or comment. What are Cookies? A cookie is a small data text file that a web site sends to your browser, which is stored on your system. The Site can only access the information from a cookie sent by the Site. We cannot access cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. Additionally, we cannot learn your e-mail address or any other information about you through the use of a cookie. The only way we would learn such information is if you specifically and voluntarily submit that information to us, for example, through a registration system, or by entering a sweepstakes or promotion. Why does the Site use cookies? The Temple Daily Telegram uses cookies to determine whether you are a registered guest and to track usage of the Site. By tracking usage, we can determine what features of the Site best serve the users. What benefits do I receive from cookies? Cookies identify you to our server, allowing you to avoid retyping your nickname, name, and e-mail address each time you access portions of the Site that are subject to registration. May I decline to accept a cookie? You may decline to accept cookies sent by the Site by selecting an option on your browser to reject cookies. However, portions of the Site that are subject to registration will continuously invite you to register, which might hamper your positive experience on the Site. Cookies enable our server to know that you are a registered user, or that you have graciously declined to register, and will eliminate the need for you to encounter the registration invitiation each time you access the Site. IP Addresses The Temple Daily Telegram logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes and to determine site usage. Your IP address does not contain personal information about you. Use of Personal Information We believe in protecting your privacy, and will not share Personal Information with any third parties , except as described in this Privacy Policy. We use Personal Information about you to improve our advertising and marketing efforts, to statistically analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to personalize the Site’s content, layout, and services. We may also use your Personal Information, such as your e-mail address or mailing address, to contact you regarding products and/or services that may be of interest to you, to respond to an inquiry from you regarding the information that we have collected, or respond to your comments and suggestions.As part of your experience on our Site, you may receive communications from us related to products and services that might interest you. While we believe these services will enhance your experience at our Site, you will at all times be able to opt out from receiving these communications, either by specifically opting out of these services or by deleting your profile from our database. Please refer to “Opting-Out” for further reference.We reserve the right to disclose Personal Information when needed to comply with the law or a legal process, cooperate with investigations of purported unlawful activities, or to identify persons violating the law. Party Collecting the Information This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose any information to other parties, whether through, for example, on-line auctions, chat rooms, personal ads, or the like, through third party services or promotions offered on or through the Site or through other web sites throughout the Internet, different policies may apply and the Temple Daily Telegram shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of such information.Our Site may carry co-branded pages, and other sites may use the Site’s name. Since The Temple Daily Telegram does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of such third parties, and the Temple Daily Telegram shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of your private information by such parties. Therefore, we encourage you to ask questions and review those parties’ privacy policies before you disclose your Personal Information to others. Links to Other Materials Third party sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under the control of the Temple Daily Telegram. The Temple Daily Telegram shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. The Temple Daily Telegram does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the Site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the Site, you do so entirely at your own risk. Children’s Privacy The Temple Daily Telegram cares about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practicable. Opting-OutWe respect your privacy and ability to choose whether to share information with us and any third party. You may choose to “opt-out” of sharing Personal Information in two ways. 1. When choosing to use certain features or services on the Site, you can choose whether to share optional Personal Information in connection with the feature or service. In some cases this may limit your access to certain areas of the Site. 2. If you receive communications from us that you prefer not to receive, you may opt out from receiving these communications, by following the "opt-out" instructions provided in the communications. SecurityThe Temple Daily Telegram maintains industry standard safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the Personal Information that you provide to us. Contacting UsIf you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at webadmin@tdtnews.com. Effective Date and Changes This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 6, 2003. The Temple Daily Telegram reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time and at our sole discretion, by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of the Site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
Latest e-Edition
Temple Daily Telegram
Eedition
Temple Daily Telegram
Most Popular
Articles
Images
ArticlesPolice: Death Thursday came from woman shooting home intruderRosebud-Lott High School nurse charged with improper relationship with studentTemple man killed in accident on State Highway 36 bridgeCity rezoning Temple Mall area for mixed useCrime Digest: Temple woman charged with sexual assault of teenBaylor Scott & White slashes 102 finance jobsUPDATE: Bell health care workers to receive vaccine first: County reports 3 deaths, breaks single-day record with 305 new coronavirus casesBell safety guidance emphasized as 57 new coronavirus cases reportedTemple shooting death under investigationElizabeth “Carolyn” (Burris) Parks, age 78, died Thursday.
Images
Featured Print Ads
© Copyright 2020 tdtnews.com, 10 South 3rd St. Temple, TX | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
